So here's what you missed on Glee:
Tina dumped Artie for Mike Chang.
There's this new kid, Sam, who's got a great voice,
We'd like to talk to you about Glee Club.
Finn thought Kurt was trying to look at him in the shower,
Maybe everyone should just start taking baths.
And that's what you missed on Glee!
All right, let's, uh, let's gather around.
Sorry I'm late, guys.
I was with Principal Figgins.
Bad news, guys.
Puckerman's in Juvvie.
It really was just a matter of time.
What did he do?
He drove his mom's Volvo through the front of a convenience store,
A... A... And when is he getting out?
Unknown.
He might be the dumbest person on this planet,
Guys!
Let's have some sympathy.
For a guy who put his needs before the team's?
We need his voice, and his bad-boy stage presence.
We can't look at this as... as a crisis.
- It's an opportunity.
- For what?
Further embarrassment and humiliation?
For welcoming our new member...
Sam Evans!
- There he is.
- How's it going?
Hey, everybody.
I'm Sam.
Sam... I am.
And I don't like green eggs and ham.
Oh, wow.
He has no game.
Okay!
This is gonna be great.
You're not going to regret joining, Sam.
Oh, good.
Sam, you sit right here.
All right!
Question for the group.
What's a duet?
A blanket.
The singers complement each other,
- Now, some people...
- Psst! He's on team gay.
No straight boy dyes his hair
Evangelista circa 1993.
You're crazy, circa 2010.
And that is what
So, this week I want you to pair up and sing a duet.
And since you guys all seemed to love our little
"Defying Gravity" diva-off,
I'm making this a competition.
What's the winner get?
Dinner for two, on me...
At Breadstix.
Breadstix!
Who you gonna sing with, Kurt?
Synced By YesCool visit us: www.MY-SUBS.com
Hi.
I'm Kurt Hummel.
Hey.
I just wanted to personally welcome you to the Glee Club.
Thanks.
Just tell me.
Look...
Maybe at your old school,
"I just stayed in the sun all summer" excuse,
I don't dye my hair, dude.
Yes, you do.
But it's just between friends.
That's not natural.
I'm gonna... go...
'cause you're kinda freaking me out.
Wait, wait.
Maybe my instincts were a little off.
Let me make it up to you.
Team up with me for the duet competition.
Listen, unless you team up with Rachel,
I am your best bet at winning.
Aren't duets supposed to be between, like, a girl and a guy?
Well, Gene Kelly and Donald
O'Connor would protest.
"Make'em Laugh"?
Sorry.
Singin' in the Rain.
1952.
Nothing.
Okay, maybe you are straight.
- What?
- Nothing. Listen, rent it,
I love your sweet lady kisses.
Mm-hmm.
It's a nice break from all that scissoring.
We should do a duet together.
We should sing Melissa Ethridge's
"Come to My Window."
First of all?
There's a lot of talking going on,
Well... I don't know,
I just... I think we just...
Okay, second of all?
I'm not making out with you because I'm in love with you
I'm only here because Puck's been in the slammer
I need something warm beneath me, or I can't digest my food.
But who are you going to sing a duet with?
Why would I want to do a duet with you?
We can't stand each other.
Look, Wheezy, I realize
I've tried to punch you a couple times,
I put weird things in your food.
But it's a new year, and you and I
I don't get what the big deal is,
Um, I'm sorry, have you been to Breadstix?
They are legally forbidden to stop bringing you breadsticks.
One time I brought a wheelbarrow,
I calleded the corporate office and got her fired.
Well, I guess our voices do sorta go together.
Mm-hmm, that's right, girl!
So if we do a duet together, we will be
- You can't do this to him.
- You're over-reacting.
If he sings with you,
Once again, your closeted homophobia seeps to the surface
Don't give me that.
Look, I know I shouldn't have used that word in your basement,
I really like you, Kurt.
But the fact of the matter is,
You have issues with me being gay, I get it.
No, actually, I don't.
I have issues with the fact that
I just want to sing with him.
Then you don't give a damn about any of us.
If he sings with you,
I guarantee, within a week,
Your call, dude.
♪ Don't go breakin' my heart. ♪
♪ I couldn't if I tried. ♪
♪ Oh honey, if I get restless... ♪
♪ Baby, you're not the kind. ♪
♪ Don't go breakin' my heart. ♪
♪ You take the weight off of me. ♪
♪ Oh honey, when you knock on my door... ♪
♪ Ooh, I gave you my key. ♪
♪ Ooh-hoo! ♪
♪ Nobody knows it. ♪
♪ But when I was down... ♪
♪ I was your clown. ♪
♪ Hoo-hoo! ♪
♪ Nobody knows it. ♪
♪ Right from the start... ♪
♪ I gave you my heart... ♪
♪ Oh... oh! ♪
♪ I gave you my heart. ♪
♪ Don't go breakin' my heart. ♪
♪ I won't go breakin' your heart. ♪
♪ Don't go breakin' my... ♪
♪ Don't go breakin' my heart. ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
We're totally going to win this thing.
I know.
Wow.
Don't be sad.
I mean, Breadstix has these vegan meatballs, they're...
They're okay.
I'm not really a nice person.
I'm selfish.
The fact is, is I'm only really generous
Yeah, but I still like you.
But you... You're so... kind, a... and open.
Well, it's made me want to be a better person.
We have to throw the competition.
I love Breadstix.
No, i... I... If we wanna win at Nationals,
Okay? He has to feel like he belongs and...
And the team has to believe in him.
Wow, Rachel,
I never seen you like this.
I'm kind of impressed.
Well, like I said...
You inspired me.
But technically, you're doing this
Okay, so I'm just gonna ignore what you just said
Right.
- I don't want to do it.
- We're duet partners. You have to sing!
I don't even know if I can sing.
Everyone knows I'm here to do one thing: Dance.
- You sing and I'll dance around you.
- No, no.
- You'll be fine.
- We're singing together.
We are gonna win that dinner at Breadstix,
Normal?
What do you mean?
We went out last night.
For dim sum.
With your mom.
All we ever do is get dim sum with your mom!
Here we go.
Hi.
So, I just want you to know
I'm really into you.
Okay.
Sorry, I'm... just a little confused.
You've never even made eye contact with me.
I know. For a while
I thought you were a robot.
I'm not saying that
I'm just saying that at Breadstix
You can get salad at dim sum.
My mom got salad last night.
There were chicken feet in it.
It was a chicken feet salad.
All I want is a normal salad
So, let me get this straight.
You want to be my girlfriend...
Because...
You like the idea of...
I just really want to get you in a stroller.
You're not listening to me.
You don't care about my needs!
Shh!
We're fighting a lot.
We should go to
Asian couples therapy.
Why does the couples therapy have to be Asian?
So, I get to tell everybody that we're dating?
Yes.
And I get a duet partner.
I don't see the big deal.
He e-mailed me, like,
60 MP3's of him singing,
The kid's good.
Look, this isn't about how good Kurt is.
Being in Glee Club is like...
It's like walking down the double yellow lines
If you get just a little off course
I got to be honest.
You're kind of confusing my head right now.
I mean, do you remember
Nationals are in New York City.
Can you imagine at it's going to be like
Most of the kids in this town have never even seen the ocean.
We'll be gods.
I joined up because I'm new here
Well, eventually you're going get popular from it,
I didn't realize you had a problem with gay dudes.
Look, I don't have a problem with gay dudes.
Everyone else does, and we're living
Well,
I gave him my word.
In my world, that's that.
Boom!
Welcome to Glee Club, lady lips.
The blueberry flavor is the worst,
I looked like a creature out of Avatar down there
I saw Avatar, like, six times.
Oh.
Anyway, you'll get used to it.
You're the head cheerleader.
Why do you even bother?
I mean, you don't need Glee Club.
I like to sing...
And the fact is
What's the point of being popular
Lor manari.
It means you have pretty eyes.
It's Nav'i...
The Avatar language.
Lor manari.
First course is served.
Heart-healthy vegan carrot soup with whole grain croutons,
Do you have any idea how hard it is to find saffron in this town?
All right, let me eat this at the table.
You could make a plaster cast of my ass
Absolutely not.
I am in charge of your care from now on.
You had a serious arrhythmia, Dad.
The doctors say you need to rest until your stress test.
You're my stress test.
Guess this means
I can't get salt?
Chin up.
What's up?
How's school?
It's fine, I guess.
There's this new kid Sam in Glee Club.
He and I are singing a duet together.
Is that a problem?
Finn practically begged me not to.
He said it'd ruin
Sam's reputation.
Well, this kid
Sam, uh...
You know, does he...
He play for your team?
Undetermined.
Oh.
Maybe Finn has a point.
You're siding with him
I was talking to Carole, and you weren't totally honest with me.
She told me that you had a crush on Finn
Is this true?
So a gay guy can't be friendly
You got to understand
So you're saying I shouldn't sing with this Sam guy
I thought you said no one pushes the Hummels around.
No one does.
I... I'm...
I'm not saying that.
I... I'm... I'm saying
Dad, you have no idea what it's like.
I am the only openly gay kid at school, in this town.
I mean, why can't I walk hand in hand
Why can't I slow-dance at my prom?
Come here.
You think I don't want those things for you?
I do.
You know, until you find somebody
♪ When I was a little girl ♪
♪ I had a rag doll. ♪
♪ Only doll
I've ever owned. ♪
♪ Now I love you just the way ♪
♪ I loved that rag doll, ♪
♪ but only now my love has grown. ♪
♪ And it gets stronger ♪
♪ in every way. ♪
♪ And it gets higher... ♪
♪ Day by day ♪
♪ Do I love you? ♪
♪ My, oh, my... ♪
♪ River deep, mountain high. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
♪ If I lost you, would I cry? ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you, baby. ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby... ♪
♪ I love you, baby. ♪
♪ Like a flower loves the spring. ♪
♪ And I love you, baby, like a robin loves to sing. ♪
♪ And I love you, baby, ♪
♪ like a schoolboy loves his bag. ♪
♪ And I love you, baby, river deep, mountain high. ♪
♪ Oh, baby... ♪
♪ Oh... baby... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh, yeah... ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
♪ Do I love you? ♪
♪ My, oh, my, yeah... ♪
♪ River deep, mountain high. ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah... ♪
♪ If I lost you, would I cry? ♪
♪ Oh, how I love you, baby. ♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby... ♪
Whoo! Yes, yes, yes.
Whoo!
Again, again, again.
Ladies, nice work.
What an incredible song.
And just so you know,
I've already bought custom bibs
You know why?
'Cause we's be going...
To Breadstix.
- Yes.
- You hear that, guys?
You have your work cut out for you.
Don't worry,
I'm not going to go all Shawshank on you.
This is kind of weird.
Guys usually don't talk to each other in here.
Well, this can't wait.
I'm setting you free.
You can do your duet with someone else in Glee,
Did I do something to offend you?
No, no, I...
It's not you, it's me.
You've been honorable, actually,
Who's that?
You know, they make special shampoo
I don't dye my hair.
Uh-huh.
This is a disaster.
Could you stop pacing?
It's stressing me out.
It's just, being the "it couple"
I-I am so stumped at how to lose this thing.
Wait, I got it.
You remember we saw
Grease and it was good,
- was that the songs were bad.
- Were bad.
Yeah.
If we want to lose, we have to do a song that's bad.
Not just a bad song, an offensive song.
Yes!
- Artie.
- Mm-hmm.
- Can we talk?
- Yeah.
- I want us to be duet partners.
- Really?
We sing really well together.
I just thought if we won,
We haven't really talked.
Well, Tina, as rich as I find it
I'll have you know that
If you'll excuse me.
Okay, guys, so...
Who is up first today?
Mr. Shue, if I may.
You may.
As many of you know,
I had a duet partner,
I'd rather not get into
Okay, so who are you going to sing a duet with?
Only the most talented member of the Glee Club: Myself.
When you're different, when you're special,
I've asked a few members of the Glee Club
How can you do a duet by yourself?
That's like vocal masturbation or something.
I will be doing a number
It's a show about embracing both the male and the female sides.
Watch and learn, Santana.
Hit it.
♪ 'Bout 20 years ago, ♪
♪ way down in New Orleans, ♪
♪ A group of fellers found ♪
♪ a new kind of music, ♪
♪ and they decided to call it ♪
♪ jazz. ♪
♪ No other sound has what this music has. ♪
♪ Before they knew it, ♪
♪ it was whizzin'
'round the world. ♪
♪ The world was ready ♪
♪ for a blue kind of music, ♪
♪ and now they play it ♪
♪ from Steamboat Springs ♪
♪ to La Paz. ♪
♪ Oh, baby, ♪
♪ won't you play me ♪
♪ Le Jazz Hot. ♪
♪ Maybe, and don't ever let it end. ♪
♪ I tell ya, friend, it's really something to hear. ♪
♪ I can't sit still ♪
♪ when there's that rhythm near me. ♪
♪ When you play me ♪
♪ Le Jazz Hot, baby, ♪
♪ you're holding my soul together. ♪
♪ Don't know whether it's morning or night. ♪
♪ Only know it sounded right. ♪
♪ So come on in and play me ♪
♪ Le Jazz Hot, ♪
♪ baby, 'cause
I love my jazz ♪
♪ hot... ♪
♪ Le... ♪
♪ Jazz... ♪
♪ Hot... ♪
Le Jazz Hot.
- Yeah!
I love astronomy.
Something about all that space
That one's Venus.
Planet of love.
It's actually Mars, planet of war.
Which one are we on?
Earth.
So why don't you come back to it
Tell me why I should be singing with you.
Okay.
Well, I want to start off with the choreography.
Singing will be easy, so I'll start playing...
All right, now get behind me.
Get behind me.
Good.
Now grab my hips.
And start swaying.
All right, now, here's the cool part.
Give me your hand.
Do you know how to play?
No.
All right, it's easy.
Just put that finger there.
Just like that.
Now do it fast back and forth.
There you go.
No.
No, I can't do this.
This year is about me.
And don't say that I'm selfish, because you have no idea
- how much I've given.
- I wasn't... I wasn't gonna...
I've been down this path before.
I know this feeling.
Like I need you.
Duets don't work for me, and I don't need you.
What I need is to find a way to keep Santana off my heels.
- I'm... I'm sorry...
- What I need is to find a way to torture Rachel.
And I need to start learning to ignore people.
And I'm sorry,
I shouldn't...
I shouldn't have tried that.
I'm sorry.
I made a mistake, and, um...
I don't want to sing with you.
I don't think I could do this.
It's the perfect song for this very situation.
Whenever you're ready, guys.
Yeah, hurry up.
I needs to get myself to Breadstix.
Don't count on it.
I'm mad at you, but you're still so hot.
Trust me, you're gonna be great.
♪ See, I really couldn't sing. ♪
♪ I could never really sing. ♪
♪ What I couldn't do is... ♪
♪ Sing. ♪
♪ I have trouble with the... ♪
♪ Note. ♪
♪ It goes all around my... ♪
♪ Throat. ♪
♪ It's a terrifying... ♪
♪ Thing. ♪
♪ See, I really couldn't... ♪
♪ Hear.
♪ Which note was lower or was... ♪
♪ Higher. ♪
♪ Which is why ♪
♪ I disappear if someone says ♪
♪ let's start a... ♪
♪ Choir. ♪
♪ Hey, when I begin to...
♪ Squeak. ♪
♪ It's a cross between a... ♪
♪ Shriek. ♪
♪ And a quiver or a... ♪
Moan. ♪
♪ It's a little like a... ♪
♪ Croak. ♪
♪ Or the record player... ♪
♪ Broke. ♪
♪ What it doesn't have is... ♪
♪ Tone. ♪
♪ Oh, I know you're thinking what a crazy... ♪
♪ Ding-a-ling. ♪
♪ But I really couldn't... ♪
♪ Sing. ♪
♪ I could never really... ♪
♪ What I couldn't do is... ♪
♪ Sing. ♪
But what I lack in pitch,
I sure make up in...
♪ Power... ♪
And all my friends say
I am perfect for the...
♪ Shower! ♪
♪ Still... I'm terrific at a... ♪
♪ Dance. ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm messing up my... ♪
♪ Pants. ♪
♪ I'm a birdie on the... ♪
♪ Wing. ♪
♪ But if I begin to... ♪
♪ Chirp. ♪
♪ They say who's the little... ♪
♪ Twerp. ♪
♪ Going pong instead of... ♪
♪ Ping. ♪
♪ And when Christmas comes, and all my friends go... ♪
♪ Caroling... ♪
♪ It is so dishearten... ♪
♪ Ning. ♪
♪ It is so disquiet... ♪
♪ Ting. ♪
♪ It is so discourage... ♪
♪ Ging. ♪
♪ Darling, please stop answer... ♪
♪ Ring. ♪
♪ See, I really couldn't... ♪
♪ Sing. ♪
♪ I could never really... ♪
♪ What I couldn't do is ♪
♪ Do re mi fa so la to do, do re mi fa so la ti do... ♪
♪ La... ♪
♪ Sing, sing, sing, sing, sing, sing... ♪
♪ Sing! ♪
Wow!
Now, that is a duet!
Thank you, Tina, for introducing us
That was good.
You tried to kiss her?
Major Glee party foul, dude.
Look, I know I shouldn't have.
She was just sending me these vibes.
And those eyes.
Hey, Quinn, can we talk?
- What do you want to talk about?
- About Sam. I... I heard
Maybe it's for the best she backed out.
I mean, if that Puckerman kid ever gets out of jail,
I'm sure you still have feelings for her, too.
No, no, no way.
I'm with Rachel now.
I mean, she's a lot shorter than Quinn
Look, th... This isn't about dating, dude.
This is about you singing with Quinn
Look, I understand that your reputation is important to you, but...
Wouldn't you want to do whatever it takes to be on top
Singing with Sam won't change that.
Oh, but winning the competition will.
And partnering with Sam is really your only shot at it.
What's your angle?
- Angle?
- What's your angle?
Me winning means you losing,
Look, I agree.
Okay? You're probably not gonna beat Finn and I,
Look, I'm not saying you're gonna win, but I'm just saying
Hey.
Listen, I was totally out of line with you.
I promise it won't happen again,
Good. Because we're gonna have to spend a lot of time together practicing
♪ Oh, oh, yay... ♪
Just like that.
Tina used to make runs look so easy, but...
- I guess they aren't for everybody.
- Wait.
♪ Oh, oh, yay... ♪
Nailed it.
I'm sorry, I can't do this.
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
Uh, why...
Why can't you do this?
I thought I was over somebody, but I...
I still think
I have feelings for them.
The Clintons?
Tina.
I'm sorry.
Wait, don't leave.
You want to get over Tina, right?
Let me help you.
What are you...
What are you doing?
I mean, you're on the football team now anyways.
So...
We're gonna get around to this at some point.
Hold up.
Am I about to lose my virginity?
Before our duet, we're gonna do it.
♪ Come give me... ♪
♪ Oh... ♪
♪ your sweetness. ♪
♪ Oh, oh... ♪
♪ Now there's you, there is no weakness. ♪
♪ Lying safe within your arms, ♪
♪ I'm born again... ♪
♪ Woman, don't you know with you I'm born again. ♪
♪ I was half, not whole.
Instead with none. ♪
♪ Reaching through this world in need of one... ♪
This isn't happening.
♪ Come show me your kindness. ♪
♪ In your arms
I know I'll find this. ♪
♪ Woman... ♪
♪ Don't you know with you, ♪
♪ I'm born again. ♪
♪ Lying safe with you, ♪
♪ I'm born a... gain... ♪
Okay, do I even need to say it?
That was really rude.
It was, like, really rude.
I seriously wanted to punch both of you.
I have to agree.
It's a great duet,
Your costume choice was a little insensitive.
Frankly...
I'm disappointed.
What?!
Are you serious?
I'm...
- Shocked.
We're... We're shocked.
I... I... I really hope that this doesn't cost us the competition.
- Yeah, uh...
- Hey.
Let's sit down.
Come.
Well,
All right.
Okay, I just want to say
I'm really excited,
I couldn't have asked for a better partner.
♪ Do you hear me? ♪
♪ I'm talking to you across the water. ♪
♪ Across the deep blue ocean, ♪
♪ under the open sky. ♪
♪ Oh, my, baby, I'm trying. ♪
♪ Boy, I hear you in my dreams. ♪
♪ I feel your whisper across the sea. ♪
♪ I keep you with me in my heart. ♪
♪ You make it easier when life gets hard. ♪
♪ I'm lucky I'm in love with my best friend. ♪
♪ Lucky to have been where I have been. ♪
♪ Lucky to be coming home again. ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ooh-ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
♪ They don't know... ♪
♪ How long it takes... ♪
♪ Waiting for love like this. ♪
♪ Every time... ♪
♪ We say good-bye... ♪
♪ I wish we had one more kiss. ♪
♪ I'll wait for you,
I promise you, ♪
♪ I will... ♪
♪ I'm... ♪
♪ Lucky I'm in love with my best friend. ♪
♪ Lucky to have been where I have been. ♪
♪ Lucky to be coming home some day. ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh ooh-ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
♪ Ooh, ooh-ooh, ooh-ooh... ♪
So frickin' charming.
♪ Ooh, ooh, ooh... ♪
You're...
You're breaking up with me?
All you wanted was a free dinner at Breadstix.
But I really wanted to go with you.
I was going to order us
I've been practicing nudging the meatballs
You used me for my voice.
That's the only reason you had sex with me.
I have it on good authority.
She's using you for your voice.
That's the only reason she had sex with you.
Wait. How did you know that?
Hi. Excuse me.
Do you know Brittany?
Cheerios! Brittany?
- Mm-hmm.
- Yeah. We had sex.
Hmm. Look,
I don't mean to be a bitch...
Well, yeah, actually, I do...
But the only thing that you can give Brittany
I know that sex doesn't mean anything to you,
After my accident,
And when I found out that I could,
You're not my partner anymore.
I told Mr. Shue I'm pulling out of the duet competition.
Artie, I didn't know.
I'm...
I'm so sorry.
Okay, since Artie and Brittany have dropped
Well, even though it looks like
Even those who didn't compete...
We do have a winner.
And the winner is...
By two votes...
Sam and Quinn.
- What?
Screw that!
I want my stix!
Ooh, let it go.
Let go. Let it go!
Unbelievable.
It was mine! No, I don't know how this happened.
Son.
Unbelievable.
This is so not a date.
We did it, babe.
Hey, I had something
I wanted to talk to you about.
Oh, please not another pregnancy.
I think that you and I are a little bit more similar than you think.
That's a terrible thing to say.
I know you're lonely.
I can't even imagine how hard it must be
We're going to win
Nationals this year,
Because we have you.
That's true.
That's twelve people who love you just
Look, I'm know you're lonely, but...
You're not alone.
So, I was wondering
I think you'll be really happy with my song selection.
It's sort of everything that both you and I love.
But the, uh, duet competition is over.
I know.
I just...
I thought this one could be for me and you.
You know, I hear they don't even make these fresh.
They fly them in frozen from some factory
I once caught some pretty sweet waves down in the Dominican.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Uh-uh.
- Come on.
It's my Matthew McConaughey impression... Come on.
Does that work on the girls where you're from?
The impressions, the bad jokes,
Uh, I don't know.
I don't know.
I went to an all-boys boarding school.
Makes sense.
It must be hard.
I think if I went through what you went through last year,
I would have transferred to a school on the moon
Okay, that... That didn't come out right. I mean,
I don't judge you or anything.
I know what it's like to have a...
Oh, holy crap.
So you...
So you are gay?
What?
No. Not at all.
When I found out
I was moving here,
I wanted to seem cool, you know?
Figured if I looked like Swayze in Point Break,
I was a surfer or something.
I didn't think it through very clearly.
So...
I put lemon juice in my hair.
I would have gotten away with it, if it hadn't been
I think it looks cute.
Really?
What are you doing?
We're not using that.
You're paying.
Why?
Because a gentleman always pays on the first date.
♪ Forget your troubles... ♪
♪ Happy days... ♪
♪ Come on get happy... ♪
♪ Are here again... ♪
♪ You better chase... ♪
♪ The skies... ♪
♪ All your cares away... ♪
♪ Above are clear again... ♪
♪ Shout hallelujah. ♪
♪ So let's sing a song... ♪
♪ Come on, get happy. ♪
♪ Of cheer again... ♪
♪ Get ready for the judgment day. ♪
♪ Happy days are here again. ♪
♪ The sun is shining, ♪
♪ come on get happy. ♪
♪ Shining now... ♪
♪ The Lord is waiting... ♪
♪ There's no one... ♪
♪ To take your hand... ♪
♪ Who can doubt it now. ♪
♪ Shout hallelujah... ♪
♪ So let's tell the world... ♪
♪ And just get happy. ♪
♪ About it now. ♪
♪ We're going... ♪
♪ Happy days... ♪
♪ To the promised land... ♪
♪ Are here again. ♪
♪ We're heading across the river. ♪
♪ Soon your cares will all be gone. ♪
♪ They'll be no more from now on. ♪
♪ From now on... ♪
♪ Forget your troubles... ♪
♪ Oh, happy days... ♪
♪ And just get happy. ♪
♪ Are here again. ♪
♪ You better chase... ♪
♪ The skies... ♪
♪ All your blues away. ♪
♪ Above are clear again. ♪
♪ Shout hallelujah... ♪
♪ So let's sing a song... ♪
♪ And just get happy. ♪
♪ Of cheer again. ♪
♪ Happy times... ♪
♪ Happy nights... ♪
♪ Happy days... ♪
♪ Are... here... again! ♪
Synced By YesCool visit us: www.MY-SUBS.com